=Revenge of Royal Princess=
= انتقام الأميرة الملكية =
=Episode 19=
= الحلقة 19 =
Witch
ساحرة
or disaster?
أم كارثة؟
It is because of you that Royal Princess cannot rest in peace.
إنه بسببك أن الأميرة الملكية لا يمكنها أن ترقد بسلام.
Really?
هل حقا؟
But Royal Princess didn't say that to me.
لكن الأميرة الملكية لم تقل ذلك لي.
No more nonsense.
لا مزيد من الهراء.
Royal Princess let me ask you
الأميرة الملكية اسمحوا لي أن أسألك
why do ou aim at me
لماذا تستهدفني
and Regent all the time.
وريجنت في كل وقت.
Is there any wild ambition?
هل هناك طموح جامح؟
Royal Princess won't let you convey such words.
لن تسمح لك الأميرة الملكية بنقل مثل هذه الكلمات.
This is
هذا هو
the peacock bow that was buried with Royal Princess.
قوس الطاووس الذي تم دفنه مع الأميرة الملكية.
Isn't it lost?
ألم تضيع؟
This is Royal Princess's favorite peacock bow when she was alive.
هذا هو الطاووس المفضل لدى Royal Princess عندما كانت على قيد الحياة.
It was taken away before.
تم أخذها بعيدا من قبل.
Prime Minister Guo.
رئيس الوزراء قوه.
If you don't watch your words,
إذا كنت لا تشاهد كلماتك ،
Royal Princess will also take you away.
الأميرة الملكية ستأخذك بعيدًا أيضًا.
Does sister have anything to tell me?
هل لدى الأخت أي شيء لتخبرني به؟
(Idiot)
(غبي)
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
I am glad that you are back.
أنا سعيد بعودتك.
Han Shu.
هان شو.
Just now Guo Yao wanted to attempt suicide for you.
الآن فقط أراد قوه ياو أن يحاول الانتحار من أجلك.
Even I was moved by her infatuation.
حتى أنني تأثرت باهتمامها.
You have been infatuated with sister and haven't married for many years.
لقد كنت مفتونًا بأختك ولم تتزوج منذ سنوات عديدة.
I will make a decision for you.
سوف أتخذ قرارا من أجلك.
How about getting married with Guo Yao?
ماذا عن الزواج من قوه ياو؟
Great, Your Royal Highness.
عظيم ، صاحب السمو الملكي.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Your Majesty don't need to worry about my affairs.
جلالة الملك لا داعي للقلق بشأن أموري.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
As long as I can stay with His Royal Highness,
طالما يمكنني البقاء مع صاحب السمو الملكي ،
I am willing to be a maid even.
أنا على استعداد لأن أكون خادمة حتى.
What a perfect match.
يا لها من تطابق مثالي.
Right, Your Royal Highness?
صحيح يا صاحب السمو الملكي؟
Sister!
أخت!
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Kneel down.
اركع للأسفل.
Your Royal Highness.
صاحب السمو الملكي.
This is Dr. Cheng who treated Royal Princess back then.
هذا هو الدكتور تشينغ الذي عالج الأميرة الملكية في ذلك الوقت.
Greetings to Your Royal Highness.
تحياتي لصاحب السمو الملكي.
Back then, Royal Princess
في ذلك الوقت ، الأميرة الملكية
had shown signs of physical exhaustion.
ظهرت عليهم علامات الإرهاق الجسدي.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
When I visited Royal Princess for the last time,
عندما زرت Royal Princess للمرة الأخيرة ،
she had less than three days to live.
كان لديها أقل من ثلاثة أيام لتعيش.
Your Royal Highness.
صاحب السمو الملكي.
I also found out that...
اكتشفت أيضًا أن ...
Say it.
قلها.
The assassin back then
القاتل في ذلك الوقت
was Royal Princess's confidant.
كان المقرب من الأميرة الملكية.
Shu.
شو.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
You knew you were going to die.
كنت تعلم أنك ستموت.
You know it all?
هل تعرف كل شيء؟
You are only concerned about Li Xie, your younger brother.
أنت مهتم فقط بـ Li Xie ، أخوك الأصغر.
You used your own life to set up a trap to save me,
لقد استخدمت حياتك الخاصة في نصب فخ لإنقاذي ،
in exchange for me being devoted to you
مقابل تكريس لي لك
and working for the Li Royal Family.
ويعمل لدى عائلة لي الملكية.
My presence was a mistake.
وجودي كان خطأ.
I shouldn't have been there.
ما كان يجب أن أكون هناك.
Good for you, sister.
جيد لك يا أختي.
So what if I did it?
إذن ماذا لو فعلت ذلك؟
What do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
You forced me to do this.
لقد أجبرتني على فعل هذا.
And you have to take it.
وعليك أن تأخذها.
(The right of communication through network)
(حق الاتصال عبر الشبكة)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)
(تنتمي حصريًا إلى Tencent.)